/*
 * @Date: 2021-08-09 14:58:55
 * @LastEditors: Junxi ZHANG
 * @LastEditTime: 2021-08-10 18:44:56
 * @FilePath: /Frontend/app/javascript/packs/quizz.js
 */

$(function () {
  start(questionNumber);

  $(".submit-answer").on("click", function (event) {

    var userAnswer = parseInt($(this).attr("id"));
    answerCheck(userAnswer);

    setTimeout(function () {
      $(".submit-answer").removeClass("correctStyle incorrectStyle");
      start(questionNumber);
    }, 1000)

    questionNumber++;
  });

});

var questionNumber = 0,
  totalCorrect = 0,
  optionFinal = 0;

var allQuestions = [{
  question: 'Who said, "My real father lost his head at Kings Landing. I made a choice, and I chose wrong."',
  choices: ["Robb Stark", "Jon Snow", "Theon Greyjoy", "Arya Stark"],
  answer: 2
}, {
  question: "What does Valar Morghulis mean?",
  choices: ["All men must die", "What is dead may never die", "Never say never", "All men must first live"],
  answer: 0
}, {
  question: "Which GOT character played Hermoine Granger's mom in Harry Potter?",
  choices: ["Melisandre", "Catelyn Stark", "Cersei Lannister", "Alerie Tyrell"],
  answer: 1
}, {
  question: 'Who said, "You knelt as boys, now rise as men of the Nights Watch."?',
  choices: ["Maester Aemon", "Eddard Stark", "Jeor Mormont", "Alliser Thorne"],
  answer: 2
}, {
  question: "What is Daenerys Targaryens brothers name?",
  choices: ["Varys", "Viserys", "Aerys", "Aegon"],
  answer: 1
}, {
  question: "What is a big fear of the Dothraki?",
  choices: ["Fire", "Salt water", "Heavy stone", "Crows"],
  answer: 1
}, {
  question: "How many swords make up the Iron Throne?",
  choices: ["500", "1000", "2000", "5000"],
  answer: 1
}, {
  question: "What were Jon Arryn's final words?",
  choices: ["Winter is coming", "Beware of the white walkers", "The seed is strong", "Beware the dwarf"],
  answer: 2
}, {
  question: "Who built the Iron Throne?",
  choices: ["Aerys the Mad King", "Aegon The Unlikely", "Aegon the Conqueror", "Aegon the Destroyer"],
  answer: 2
}, {
  question: "Which knight takes a lance through the neck while jousting?",
  choices: ["Ser Hugh of the Vale", "Ser Barristan Selmy", "Ser Ilyn Payne", "Ser Gregor Clegane"],
  answer: 0
}];

var result = [{
  image: "http://reactiongifs.me/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/tyrion-lannister-eyebrows-game-of-thrones.gif",
  comment: " Wowzers!"
}, {
  image: "http://www.reactiongifs.us/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/GoT_joffrey_approves.gif",
  comment: " Not bad."
}, {
  image: "http://imagesmtv-a.akamaihd.net/uri/mgid:file:http:shared:mtv.com/news/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/eyeroll-1429202565.gif",
  comment: " You disappoint me child."
}, {
  image: "http://imagesmtv-a.akamaihd.net/uri/mgid:file:http:shared:mtv.com/news/wp-content/uploads/2015/06/seeaspider-1433860136.gif",
  comment: " Valar Morghulis."
}];


// continue with next question or end
var start = function (questionNumber) {
  $('h2').hide().fadeIn(400);

  if (questionNumber !== allQuestions.length) {
    question(questionNumber);
  } else {
    end();
  }
};

// show question and possible answers
function question(questionNum) {
  $("h2").text(allQuestions[questionNum].question);

  $.each(allQuestions[questionNum].choices, function (i, answers) {
    $("#" + i).html(answers);
  });
};

function end() {
  finalImage();
  $("ul").hide();
  $("h2").text("You scored " + totalCorrect + " out of " + allQuestions.length + ". " + result[optionFinal].comment);
  $("#image").html('<img src=' + result[optionFinal].image + ' alt="">').fadeIn(1000);
  $("#back-container").show();
  sendScore();
};

// result image accourding to correct answers
function finalImage() {
  if (totalCorrect < allQuestions.length && totalCorrect >= (allQuestions.length * .7)) {
    optionFinal = 1;
  } else if (totalCorrect <= (allQuestions.length * .6) && totalCorrect >= (allQuestions.length * .2)) {
    optionFinal = 2;
  } else if (totalCorrect !== allQuestions.length) {
    optionFinal = 3;
  }
}

function sendScore() {
  $("#back").on( "click", function () {
    score = totalCorrect.toString() + '/' + allQuestions.length.toString();
    window.location.href='/candidat/partiel/profil?identity='+ score;
  });
}

function answerCheck(userAnswer) {
  var correctAnswer = allQuestions[questionNumber].answer;

  if (userAnswer === correctAnswer) {
    $("#" + userAnswer).addClass("correctStyle");
    totalCorrect++;
  } else {
    $("#" + userAnswer).addClass("incorrectStyle");
  }
};